Ahmed Alhisan

software engineering

Experienced software engineer with a passion for developing innovative programs that expedite the efficiency and effectiveness of organizational success. Well-versed in technology and writing code to create systems that are reliable and user-friendly. I have full commitment to work hard and improve my skills.

Alhisan.Swe@gmail.com

0535991010

Riyadh, Saudi arabia

github.com/AhmedAlhisan



EDUCATION

Software Engineer

King Saud University / Riyadh

Riyadh



WORK EXPERIENCE

ProgrammerMinistry of Defense

09/2020 - Present

Riyadh

Tasks

- System Analsis.
- Coding (Front-End / Back-End).
- Testing.
- Deployment Windows Server 2019.
- Maintenance.
- Working with Stakeholders.

Programmer - Tmheer ProgramDolf Technology

01/2019 - 06/2019

Khobar

E learning customization platform.

Tasks

- ▶ Ubuntu 16.04.
- Open-Edx Customiziation.
- Python Back-End.
- Python/Django.



Django 4 With ExampleFourth Edition



English
Full Professional Proficiency

Arabic

Native or Bilingual Proficiency



CERTIFICATES

Front end nanodgree - UDACITY (03/2023 - Present)

Deep with JavaScript / Web APIs Asynchronous/Node Express JS

Web Development Python-Django - TUWAIQ ACADDEMY (01/2023 - 03/2023)

Working Deep with python / Django and DataBase With ORM.

Data analysis - MISK ACADDEMY

Working with Excel & Tableau.



PROJECTS.

Rent Caravans platform

Platform helping users to find caravans for rent, by showing the newst Caravans with fair price also support who want to invest by his caravans For individuals and groups.

Track Employee Courses and Mandates

Platform helping management department, to assign, courses and mandates, for employees according to employees knowledge progress, and achievements also provide statistics for all employees.

Portfolio

About me - Project - CV Download -Blog Section - replay for blog control content by Admin.



TECHNICAL SKILLS

PYTHON Django 4.1

postman test API

API Rest

C#

ASP.NET

HTML5

CSS3

JAVAScript

Bootstrap

SQL Server

PstgreSQL

GitHub

Git

Software Development Life Cycle [SDLC]

Deployment

System Analyst



SOFT SKILLS

Time management.

Communication.

Problem-solving.

Teamwork.

Work Ethic

Attention to Detail